Guide to the Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, Records
Stanford University. Libraries.
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
Stanford University, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, records
1920-1991
1960-1991
SC0133
Stanford University. Office of the Dean of Student Affairs.
Stanford University
48.5 Linear feet
Administrative office files, 1953-1991; minutes and supporting materials of various university committees, 1947-1972; Judicial Council minutes, correspondence, and other disciplinary records, 1920-1970; placement files, 1961-1983; and correspondence and other records pertaining to residential education, Tresidder Memorial Union, minority affairs, and student disruptions, 1967-1983. Deans represented in these records include John E. Hanson (1965-69) and James W. Lyons (1972-1991).
Department of Special Collections and University Archives Green Library 557 Escondido Mall Stanford, CA 94305-6064 Email: specialcollections@stanford.edu Phone: (650) 725-1022 URL: http://library.stanford.edu/spc
Administrative Information
Provenance
Administrative transfers, Office of the Dean of Student Affairs, 1975-1991.
Information about Access
Restricted: for more information see the archivist.
Biographical/Historical Sketch
The Dean of Student Affairs, formerly the Dean of Students, was reorganized in 1991 as the Office of the Vice President for Student Resources.
Description of the Collection
Administrative office files, 1953-1991; minutes and supporting materials of various university committees, 1947-1972; Judicial Council minutes, correspondence, and other disciplinary records, 1920-1970; placement files, 1961-1983; and correspondence and other records pertaining to residential education, Tresidder Memorial Union, minority affairs, and student disruptions, 1967-1983. Deans represented in these records include John E. Hanson (1965-69) and James W. Lyons (1972-1991).
Access Terms
Associated Students of Stanford University.; Hanson, John E.; Lyons, James W.; Stanford University. Office of the Dean of Student Affairs.; Students--Political activity.
Collection Contents
- Original Accession, 1920-1980
  - General Files
    - Action - University Year for, Undated (Box 1, Folder 1)
    - Address list policy (University), Undated (Box 1, Folder 2)
    - Accreditation report, 1969 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Admissions, Undated (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Affirmative Action program, Undated (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Air Force Academy, Undated (Box 1, Folder 6)
    - Alumni association and relations, Undated (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - American Council on Education - correspondence, Undated (Box 1, Folder 8)
    - Annual fund drive, Undated (Box 1, Folder 9)
    - Assistant to Pres. Mex. Amer. Aff. Search Cte., Undated (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - Association of American Colleges, 1968-1969 (Box 1, Folder 11)
    - ASSU Art Board, Undated (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - ASSU Constitution and by-laws, Undated (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - ASSU, 1969-1970 (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - ASSU, 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - ASSU - Allocation of funds, Undated (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - ASSU - General, Undated (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - ASSU - President, Undated (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - ASSU - Student Fin. Mgr., Before 1969 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - ASSU - Student Fin. Mgr. re: student fee allocation, Undated (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - ASSU travel service, Undated (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Association of Student Governments, Undated (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Athletics, Department of, Undated (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Attorney General, Undated (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Attrition report, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - B - General correspondence, Undated (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - Bail fund, Undated (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - Band and choir, Undated (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - Biology department, Undated (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - Birthday cake agency, Stanford, Undated (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Black Student Union, Undated (Box 3, Folder 8)
    - Bookstore, Undated (Box 3, Folder 9)
    - Building 10 (Rebuilding), Undated (Box 3, Folder 10)
    - Business affairs office, Undated (Box 3, Folder 11)
    - Business affairs office, university housing, Undated (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - Business and finance, Undated (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Business office staff meeting, Undated (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Business, School of, 1953-1968 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - California Council for the Academic Community (CCAC), Undated (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - California penal code, Undated (Box 3, Folder 17)
    - Campaign money, 1971 (Box 3, Folder 18)
    - Campus disruption policy, Undated (Box 3, Folder 19)
    - Campus disruptions, Faculty consultative group on, Undated (Box 3, Folder 20)
    - Campus report, Undated (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Campus security lighting, Undated (Box 4, Folder 2)
    - Cardinals board, Undated (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - Chaparral (suspension), 1960-1961 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Children's center of the Stanford community, Undated (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Chinese club house, Undated (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - Civil defense, Undated (Box 4, Folder 7)
    - Clinics, Undated (Box 4, Folder 8)
    - Cluster III - Accounts, Undated (Box 4, Folder 9)
    - Cluster III, 1967-1972 (Box 4, Folder 10)
    - Coalition for academic community, Undated (Box 4, Folder 11)
    - College guide, Undated (Box 4, Folder 12)
    - College student personnel institute, Undated (Box 4, Folder 13)
    - Colloquium series, Undated (Box 5, Folder 1)
    - Communications, Dept. of, Undated (Box 5, Folder 2)
    - Comparable institutional data, Undated (Box 5, Folder 3)
    - Complicity statements, November 1 demonstration, Undated (Box 5, Folder 4)
    - Conferences, Undated (Box 5, Folder 5)
    - Conferences, off campus, Undated (Box 5, Folder 6)
    - Contraceptives, Undated (Box 5, Folder 7)
    - Controller's office, Undated (Box 5, Folder 8)
    - Convocation on racism, Undated (Box 5, Folder 9)
    - Cowell health service, Undated (Box 5, Folder 10)
    - Cowell student health service, Undated (Box 5, Folder 11)
    - Cowell task force, Undated (Box 5, Folder 12)
    - Crank letters, Undated (Box 5, Folder 13)
    - Credit union, Undated (Box 5, Folder 14)
    - D - General correspondence, Undated (Box 6, Folder 1)
    - Danforth foundation, Undated (Box 6, Folder 2)
    - Dean of students - General, Undated (Box 6, Folder 3)
    - Dean of students - Reorganization, Undated (Box 6, Folder 4)
    - Dean of students office - Reports to President's office, Undated (Box 6, Folder 5)
    - Dean of students search committee, Undated (Box 6, Folder 6)
    - Dean of students - Space, Undated (Box 6, Folder 7)
    - Dean of students - Staff minutes, Undated (Box 6, Folder 8)
    - Demonstration houses, Undated (Box 6, Folder 9)
    - Demonstration policy, Undated (Box 6, Folder 10)
    - Demonstrations, Undated (Box 6, Folder 11)
    - Dillingham - Grass roots, Undated (Box 7, Folder 1)
    - Discrimination, Undated (Box 7, Folder 2)
    - Discussion Topics - 1, Undated (Box 7, Folder 3)
    - Discussion Topics - 2, Undated (Box 7, Folder 4)
    - Discussion Topics - 3, Undated (Box 7, Folder 5)
    - Disruption plans - Libraries, Undated (Box 7, Folder 6)
    - Disruptions, Undated (Box 7, Folder 7)
    - Drug abuse program, Undated (Box 7, Folder 8)
    - Drug proposal - the Bridge, Undated (Box 7, Folder 9)
    - Drugs: Clippings and literature (and alcohol), Undated (Box 7, Folder 10)
    - Drugs: General, Undated (Box 7, Folder 11)
    - Drugs: Policy, Undated (Box 8, Folder 1)
    - E - General correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 2)
    - East Bay mothers club, Undated (Box 8, Folder 3)
    - Eating clubs, Undated (Box 8, Folder 4)
    - Education, School of, Undated (Box 8, Folder 5)
    - Electrical engineering, Undated (Box 8, Folder 6)
    - El Toro eating club, Undated (Box 8, Folder 7)
    - Emergency procedures, Undated (Box 8, Folder 8)
    - Encounter, Undated (Box 8, Folder 9)
    - English department, Undated (Box 8, Folder 10)
    - Executive Committee of the Academic Council, Undated (Box 8, Folder 11)
    - The Experiment, Undated (Box 8, Folder 12)
    - F - General correspondence, Undated (Box 8, Folder 13)
    - Faculty Housing, Undated (Box 8, Folder 14)
    - Federal Legislation - "Anti-Riot provisions", Undated (Box 9, Folder 1)
    - Film series - A, Summer, 1966 (Box 9, Folder 2)
    - Finance, Vice President for, Undated (Box 9, Folder 3)
    - Financial aid office, Undated (Box 9, Folder 4)
    - Financial awards (external), Committee on, Undated (Box 9, Folder 5)
    - Financial director, J.P. Smith, Undated (Box 9, Folder 6)
    - Fire department, Undated (Box 9, Folder 7)
    - Flying club, Undated (Box 9, Folder 8)
    - Folk dancers, Undated (Box 9, Folder 9)
    - Food service, 1965 September-1971 (Box 9, Folder 10)
    - Food service report, Undated (Box 9, Folder 11)
    - Foreign scholarship commission, 1964-1965 (Box 9, Folder 12)
    - Foreign students roster, Undated (Box 10, Folder 1)
    - Foreign visitors, Undated (Box 10, Folder 2)
    - Fraternities, Undated (Box 10, Folder 3)
    - Fraternity housing, Undated (Box 10, Folder 4)
    - Freshman class survey, Undated (Box 10, Folder 5)
    - Freshman convocation, Undated (Box 10, Folder 6)
    - Freshman seminar, Undated (Box 10, Folder 7)
    - Fundamental standard commission, 1962-1971 (Box 10, Folder 8)
    - Fundraising - Students, Undated (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - G - General correspondence, Undated (Box 11, Folder 1)
    - General secretary, 1969 (Box 11, Folder 2)
    - General studies, Undated (Box 11, Folder 3)
    - Glee club, Undated (Box 11, Folder 4)
    - Graduate division, Undated (Box 11, Folder 5)
    - Graduate School of Business, Undated (Box 11, Folder 6)
    - Graduate Students Association, Undated (Box 11, Folder 7)
    - Graduate Students Association, Undated (Box 11, Folder 8)
    - Graduate Students AF, Undated (Box 11, Folder 9)
    - Graduate Students Union, Undated (Box 11, Folder 10)
    - Grants, Undated (Box 11, Folder 11)
    - Grass Roots, Undated (Box 11, Folder 12)
    - Grievance procedure for T.A., Undated (Box 11, Folder 13)
    - Grove project, Undated (Box 11, Folder 14)
    - Guest in residence, Undated (Box 12, Folder 1)
    - H - General correspondence, Undated (Box 12, Folder 2)
    - Handbooks - Other organizations, Undated (Box 12, Folder 3)
    - Hanson, John E., Dean - Correspondence, 1965-1966 (Box 12, Folder 4)
    - Hanson, John E., Correspondence, 1966-1967 (Box 12, Folder 5)
    - Hanson, John E., Correspondence, 1967-1968 (Box 12, Folder 6)
    - Hanson, John E., Correspondence, 1968-1969 (Box 12, Folder 7)
    - Health office (Safety office), 1961-1970 (Box 13, Folder 1)
    - Health service advisory committee, 1963 (Box 13, Folder 2)
    - Health service - General, 1946-1965 (Box 13, Folder 3)
    - Health service - Supplemental insurance, 1958-1971 (Box 13, Folder 4)
    - Heritage fund, 1967-1968 (Box 13, Folder 5)
    - Hiking trails, Undated (Box 13, Folder 6)
    - Hillel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 7)
    - History, Undated (Box 13, Folder 8)
    - Homecoming, 1953-1966 (Box 13, Folder 9)
    - Hospital admissions, Undated (Box 13, Folder 10)
    - Hostel, Undated (Box 13, Folder 11)
    - Hostel locations, Undated (Box 13, Folder 12)
    - Housing (committees), Undated (Box 14, Folder 1)
    - Housing coordination, Undated (Box 14, Folder 2)
    - Housing - Escondido (Memos from F.E. Gallagher), Undated (Box 14, Folder 3)
    - Housing - Escondido (Memos from E.A. Scoles), Undated (Box 14, Folder 4)
    - Housing - New undergraduate living ideas, Committee on, Undated (Box 14, Folder 5)
    - Housing - Planning, Undated (Box 14, Folder 6)
    - Housing policy, Undated (Box 14, Folder 7)
    - Housing problems, Committee on, 1969-1970 (Box 14, Folder 8)
    - HUAC investigation, Undated (Box 14, Folder 9)
    - Human bio, Undated (Box 14, Folder 10)
    - Humanities and Sciences, School of, Undated (Box 14, Folder 11)
    - Humphrey visit, 1967 February 20 (Box 14, Folder 12)
    - Huston house, Undated (Box 14, Folder 13)
    - I - General correspondence, Undated (Box 14, Folder 14)
    - IBM, Undated (Box 14, Folder 15)
    - ID card policy: students, staff, Undated (Box 14, Folder 16)
    - Ideas for exchanges, Undated (Box 14, Folder 17)
    - Identification cards, Undated (Box 14, Folder 18)
    - I.I.R., 1963 January-1965 August (Box 15, Folder 1)
    - I.I.R., 1965 September-1968 (Box 15, Folder 2)
    - I.I.R., Communist youth festival, Undated (Box 15, Folder 3)
    - India Association, Undated (Box 15, Folder 4)
    - Information book, Undated (Box 15, Folder 5)
    - Information bulletin, Undated (Box 15, Folder 6)
    - Information - Requests, Undated (Box 15, Folder 7)
    - Injunction, Notice of preliminary, Undated (Box 15, Folder 8)
    - Institute of International Relations, Undated (Box 15, Folder 9)
    - Inter-Club Council - Eating clubs, 1947-1966 (Box 15, Folder 10)
    - Interdepartmental mail, Undated (Box 15, Folder 11)
    - International center, Undated (Box 15, Folder 12)
    - International center, Undated (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - Issues, Undated (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - J - General correspondence, Undated (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - Japanese Students Association, Undated (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - Jaycees Distinguished Services Awards, Undated (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - Job, Undated (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - Judicial body, Interim, Undated (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - Judicial competence, 1964-1965 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - Judicial procedures, 1963-1965 March (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - Judicial procedures, 1965 April-1966 March (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - Judicial procedures, 1966 April-1968 (Box 16, Folder 11)
    - Judicial records, Undated (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - Junior faculty in Escondido Village, Undated (Box 17, Folder 1)
    - Junior Miss, Undated (Box 17, Folder 2)
    - Junipero - Wilbur Hall, Undated (Box 17, Folder 3)
    - K - General correspondence, Undated (Box 17, Folder 4)
    - Kappa Alpha, Undated (Box 17, Folder 5)
    - Kappa Sigma, Undated (Box 17, Folder 6)
    - King, Martin Luther, Fund, Undated (Box 17, Folder 7)
    - King, Martin Luther, Fund drives, Undated (Box 17, Folder 8)
    - King's mobilization, Undated (Box 17, Folder 9)
    - KZSU, Undated (Box 17, Folder 10)
    - L - General correspondence, Undated (Box 17, Folder 11)
    - Lagunita Court, Undated (Box 17, Folder 12)
    - LASSU General, Undated (Box 17, Folder 13)
    - LASSU minutes and agenda, 1966-1967 (Box 17, Folder 14)
    - Law association, Undated (Box 17, Folder 15)
    - Law, School of, 1953-1971 (Box 17, Folder 16)
    - Leadership development program, Ref., 1969 (Box 18, Folder 1)
    - Leadership development program, 1970-1972 (Box 18, Folder 2)
    - Legal defense committee, Undated (Box 18, Folder 3)
    - Legislative and judicial charter, Undated (Box 18, Folder 4)
    - Libel insurance, Undated (Box 18, Folder 5)
    - Liquor policy, Undated (Box 18, Folder 6)
    - Liquor policy, Undated (Box 18, Folder 7)
    - Liquor searches, Undated (Box 18, Folder 8)
    - M - General correspondence, Undated (Box 18, Folder 9)
    - Manzanita, Undated (Box 18, Folder 10)
    - Marriage certifications, Undated (Box 18, Folder 11)
    - Married student housing office, Undated (Box 18, Folder 12)
    - McClellan subcommitee hearing, Undated (Box 18, Folder 13)
    - Meal associate program, Undated (Box 18, Folder 14)
    - MECHA, Undated (Box 18, Folder 15)
    - Mechanical engineering department, Undated (Box 18, Folder 16)
    - Medicine, School of, Undated (Box 18, Folder 17)
    - Memorial church, Undated (Box 18, Folder 18)
    - Mental health organization, Undated (Box 18, Folder 19)
    - Mid-Peninsula Free University, Undated (Box 18, Folder 20)
    - Minority affairs, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 1)
    - Model United Nations, 1956-1971 (Box 19A, Folder 2)
    - Moratorium, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 3)
    - Moses, Lincoln, Memo from, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 4)
    - Mothers' club, 1953-1970 (Box 19A, Folder 5)
    - N - General correspondence, Undated (Box 19A, Folder 6)
    - NACUA (National Association of College and University Attornies), Undated (Box 19B, Folder 7)
    - NASPA - National Association of Student Personnel - old, Undated (Box 19B, Folder 8)
    - NASPA, 1970-1971 (Box 19B, Folder 9)
    - National Science Foundation program, Undated (Box 19B, Folder 10)
    - National Student Association (see also Assn. of Student Govts.), 1964 (Box 19B, Folder 11)
    - NCE Today, Undated (Box 20, Folder 1)
    - News Service, 1966 (Box 20, Folder 2)
    - News Service Pre-Reg, 1965 (Box 20, Folder 3)
    - Non-Violent House, Undated (Box 20, Folder 4)
    - O - General correspondence, Undated (Box 20, Folder 5)
    - October 15 moratorium, Undated (Box 20, Folder 6)
    - Old Union, Undated (Box 20, Folder 7)
    - Old Union building - Early planning, Undated (Box 20, Folder 8)
    - Old Union sit-in, 1968 May (Box 21, Folder 1)
    - Open house regulations, Undated (Box 21, Folder 2)
    - Overseas campuses, Undated (Box 21, Folder 3)
    - Overseas campuses - Austria, Undated (Box 21, Folder 4)
    - Overseas campuses - Britain, Undated (Box 21, Folder 5)
    - Overseas campuses - France, Undated (Box 21, Folder 6)
    - Overseas campuses - Germany, Undated (Box 21, Folder 7)
    - Overseas campuses - Italy, Undated (Box 21, Folder 8)
    - Overseas campuses - Spain, Undated (Box 21, Folder 9)
    - P - General correspondence, Undated (Box 21, Folder 10)
    - PACE, Undated (Box 21, Folder 11)
    - Palo Alto Unified School District, Undated (Box 21, Folder 12)
    - Parietal rules, Undated (Box 21, Folder 13)
    - Parking, Undated (Box 22A, Folder 1)
    - Patent policy and licensing prg., Undated (Box 22A, Folder 2)
    - Peace Corps, Undated (Box 22A, Folder 3)
    - Peace Corps, 1967 February-1972 (Box 22A, Folder 4)
    - Personal behavior discussions, Undated (Box 22A, Folder 5)
    - Personnel office, 1966-1971 (Box 22A, Folder 6)
    - Physical education for men, Undated (Box 22B, Folder 7)
    - Physical education for women, Undated (Box 22B, Folder 8)
    - Physical plant, 1968-1970 (Box 22B, Folder 9)
    - Physics, Dept. of, 1968 (Box 22B, Folder 10)
    - Placement service, 1969-1970 (Box 22B, Folder 11)
    - Placement service, Student employment, 1970-1971 (Box 22B, Folder 12)
    - Placement service, Annual report, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 1)
    - Placement service, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 2)
    - Police Dept. Correspondence, 1961-1971 (Box 23, Folder 3)
    - Police Dept., Reports, 1969-1971 (Box 23, Folder 4)
    - Political activity, 1970-1971 (Box 23, Folder 5)
    - Political action, 1969-1970 (Box 23, Folder 6)
    - Political union, 1949-1967 (Box 23, Folder 7)
    - Political union, 1964-1967 (Box 23, Folder 8)
    - Post office, 1962-1970 (Box 24, Folder 1)
    - Pre-law advising, 1968-1969 (Box 24, Folder 2)
    - Pre-reg, 1967-1969 (Box 24, Folder 3)
    - Pre-registration, 1970-1971 (Box 24, Folder 4)
    - Presidential advisory committees, 1968 (Box 24, Folder 5)
    - President's office, 1963-1970 (Box 24, Folder 6)
    - President's office (Glaser), 1968 (Box 24, Folder 7)
    - President's office (Glover), 1965-1971 (Box 24, Folder 8)
    - President's office (Lyman), 1970-1973 (Box 24, Folder 9)
    - President's office (Pitzer), 1968-1970 (Box 24, Folder 10)
    - President's office (Schwartz), 1970 (Box 24, Folder 11)
    - President's weekly meeting, 1970-1972 (Box 24, Folder 12)
    - Princeton plan, 1970 (Box 24, Folder 13)
    - Problem areas, 1969-1970 (Box 24, Folder 14)
    - Product engineering, Undated (Box 24, Folder 15)
    - Project information center, Undated (Box 24, Folder 16)
    - Project planning meeting, Undated (Box 24, Folder 17)
    - Publications - Blotter (Stanford), 1965-1967 (Box 24, Folder 18)
    - Publications Board - General, 1959-1969 (Box 24, Folder 19)
    - Publications - Carnegie Quarterly, Undated (Box 25, Folder 1)
    - Publications - Chaparral, 1958 (Box 25, Folder 2)
    - Publications - Chaparral, 1959-1960 (Box 25, Folder 3)
    - Publications - Chaparral, 1961-1966 (Box 25, Folder 4)
    - Publications - College law bulletin, Undated (Box 25, Folder 5)
    - Publications - Federal notes, Undated (Box 25, Folder 6)
    - Publications - Ford Found. Letter, Undated (Box 25, Folder 7)
    - Publications - Higher Education and National Affairs, Undated (Box 25, Folder 8)
    - Publications - National On Campus Report, Undated (Box 25, Folder 9)
    - Publications - News Letter, The, Undated (Box 25, Folder 10)
    - Publications - Quad (Stanford), 1953-1967 (Box 25, Folder 11)
    - Publications - Quarterly Review, Undated (Box 25, Folder 12)
    - Publications - Sequoia, 1963-1967 (Box 25, Folder 13)
    - Publications - Stanford Daily, 1948-1959 (Box 25, Folder 14)
    - Publications - Stanford Daily, 1960-1964 (Box 25, Folder 15)
    - Publications - Storke, 1969 (Box 26, Folder 1)
    - Publications - University Bulletin, Univ. of California, Undated (Box 26, Folder 2)
    - Publications - Wiche, Undated (Box 26, Folder 3)
    - Publications - Workshop (Stanford), 1965-1967 (Box 26, Folder 4)
    - Public benefit policy, 1970 (Box 26, Folder 5)
    - Public events, Dept. of, 1964-1971 (Box 26, Folder 6)
    - Public safety, Director of, 1968-1970 (Box 26, Folder 7)
    - Q - General correspondence, Undated (Box 26, Folder 8)
    - R - General correspondence, 1966-1969 (Box 26, Folder 9)
    - Raveswood tutorial project, 1966 (Box 26, Folder 10)
    - Recommendations - Telles, Undated (Box 26, Folder 11)
    - Recycling, 1971-1972 (Box 26, Folder 12)
    - Red Cross, 1953-1968 (Box 26, Folder 13)
    - Registrar, 1961-1972 (Box 26, Folder 14)
    - "Religion on campus" - CBS TV special, Undated (Box 26, Folder 15)
    - Religious activities, Committee on, Undated (Box 26, Folder 16)
    - Repertory Theater, 1965-1966 (Box 26, Folder 17)
    - Research Department, 1969-1972 (Box 26, Folder 18)
    - Residence advisory committee, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 1)
    - Residence configuration, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 2)
    - Residence directors' minutes, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 3)
    - Residence hall security, 1970 (Box 27, Folder 4)
    - Residence operating committee, 1969-1970 (Box 27, Folder 5)
    - Residence staffing, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 6)
    - Residence staff orientation, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 7)
    - Residences - Coeducational corridors, 1971-1973 (Box 27, Folder 8)
    - Residences - Housing - Discrimination, 1961-1968 (Box 27, Folder 9)
    - Residences - Minority Student Housing, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 10)
    - Residences - Staff, 1970-1971 (Box 27, Folder 11)
    - Residences - General, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 1)
    - Residences - Resident fellows and student staff, 1970-1972 (Box 28, Folder 2)
    - Room and board rates, 1970-1971 (Box 28, Folder 3)
    - Room and board task force, 1971 (Box 28, Folder 4)
    - ROTC, Undated (Box 28, Folder 5)
    - ROTC and military science, Undated (Box 28, Folder 6)
    - S - General correspondence, Undated (Box 28, Folder 7)
    - SAIP - Correspondence, Undated (Box 28, Folder 8)
    - SAIP material, Undated (Box 29, Folder 1)
    - Samples, Undated (Box 29, Folder 2)
    - Selective service, Undated (Box 29, Folder 3)
    - Selective service (National service office), 1965-1968 (Box 29, Folder 4)
    - Senior - Officers, events, etc., Undated (Box 29, Folder 5)
    - SES - Asilomar and counseling, Undated (Box 29, Folder 6)
    - Sex, Undated (Box 29, Folder 7)
    - Siena, Jim: Memos from, Undated (Box 29, Folder 8)
    - Sierra Camp, Undated (Box 29, Folder 9)
    - Sigma Chi, 1966 March (Box 29, Folder 10)
    - Sigma Chi, 1966 April-December (Box 30, Folder 1)
    - Sit-In (President's Office), 1966 (Box 30, Folder 2)